♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 31=
What's done can't be undone.
Now, I just want to figure out
the truth of the devils' revolt
to propitiate the dead of Daze Mountain.
Time to vindicate Yin, too.
Didn't His Godship
ask Her Majesty Feng Yuan to persuade
the Phoenix Queen?
How could it have no effect?
Feng Yuan sent a reply.
She said that the Phoenix Queen
is truly persistent.
She is determined to uncover
the truth of the past.
Didn't His Godship ask me
to break off the engagement?
Why did he suddenly care about
the Phoenix Queen so much?
What is exactly going on here?
Your Majesty.
Elder Feng Yun.
Her Ladyship will meet the Wind Lord
today and you're invited, too.
(Hong Yi, I've invited Wind Lord
to Fengyi Palace for verification)
(of the truth about Yin's entanglement with
devils a thousand years ago. Feng Yin)
I have to go to Wutong Island now.
Go to the Pear Blossom Cottage and
tell Yan Shuang that I will arrive later.
Yes.
(Beautiful Spring After the Snow)
Hong Yi.
Her Ladyship is so charming.
One is the God of Qingchi Palace.
The other is the Demon King
of Xuanjing Palace.
They are not only prestigious,
but also handsome.
Whom do you think Her Ladyship
will ultimately choose?
It must be the Demon King.
He was personally invited by
Her Ladyship by writing a letter.
I think Her Ladyship won't make a choice.
She will get both of them.
Yes.
- Your Godship.
- Don't.
Well…
Your Godship, don't get in.
Elder Feng Yun,
why didn't you stop that guy just now?
Her Majesty said they would investigate
the case about Demon King Lin Sen.
Irreverent persons shall not enter
without invitation.
His Godship has been investigating
this matter for a thousand years.
How could he be an irreverent person?
Her Ladyship specifically instructed that
only the Demon King can enter the palace.
This is the clue that
God Yuan Qi found at that time.
(Confidential)
Although there are some
useful information,
it couldn't prove Yin's innocence.
(The old scar on the right arm of the Wind Lord
can prove what he said is true)
Wind Lord, did you suffer any injuries
back then?
Hong Yi had a battle with me when
escaping from Immortal-locking Tower.
This scar was left at that time.
Yin, let's go.
This is indeed the scar left by
my Fire Palm.
It will take several days to
recover the spiritual power.
Even if the sword was not stolen,
you cannot possibly have the power to
kill the Demon King after injury.
I thought of this when Yuan Qi
and I analyzed it.
I didn't want the conflict to escalate due to
the incident of Hong Yi hurting me.
(When His Majesty Lin Sen was assassinated,)
So my injury was not announced.
(the surrounding guards
all show signs of amnesia)
At that time, the Immortal Realm
had already set up the super barrier.
If there were no assistance
from the immortals,
how could Qing Lin easily get close to
His Majesty Lan Feng
without causing any disturbance?
Could it be Feng Ming?
With Feng Ming's immortal power,
it would be impossible for him to do this.
There must be a mole more
powerful than him in the Immortal Realm.
God Yuan Qi has informed me that
he will find evidence soon.
I believe the day when the truth
is revealed is not far away.
Did His Godship find out anything?
He hasn't communicated the details
with me yet,
but he said he has his own arrangements.
Since both you and His Godship
are investigating this matter,
I think it's better to work together
and pool our efforts.
If you don't mind, let me...
Thank you, Wind Lord. Don't bother.
I have always been doing things alone.
I don't like to cooperate with others.
However, I will reinvestigate this
thousand-year-old case in a few days.
I hope Your Lordship lends
a helping hand at that time.
This is my duty.
By the way, Hong Yi,
you go find Yan Shuang.
When the time is ripe, I will need her
to come to the Heavenly Palace.
Okay.
Oh my.
I forgot I had an appointment
with Yan Shuang today.
Today?
Why don't you go now?
(Beautiful Spring After the Snow)
(Could it be that Jiu forgot about this?)
(Forget it. I'll go find him myself.)
Hong Yun.
Your Highness,
you don't have to wait anymore.
His Majesty
has something important to do.
He asked me to tell you.
Where did he go?
His Majesty went to Wutong Island
to find the Phoenix Queen.
When did he go?
In the early morning when he received
Phoenix Queen's letter.
Did he say when he will come back?
No.
I don't think he can come back tonight.
Don't wait for him here anymore.
The Pear Blossom Cottage
is right in the Mortal Realm.
After you succeed as the Eagle Queen.
you can come and go as you please.
You don't need to waste time
with me here.
These thousands of years
are ultimately wasted.
Hong Yi,
you truly don't have me in your heart.
(That's fine.)
(I'll consider this as the answer
he gave me.)
Yan Shuang! Sorry, I'm late.
See what I brought for you.
Yan Shuang!
Your Majesty.
Where is Yan Shuang?
She probably went to the city.
To the city?
♪Witness several rounds of
bright moon rolls♪
♪Never touched
by the worldly wind and snow♪
♪Endless yearning♪
♪Is hidden in the day and night♪
♪Time passes by in an instant♪
♪Let the longing be as high as the sky♪
♪May I become a wisp of smoke,
lingering around your lips♪
♪A drop of tear♪
♪Carries many karmic cycles♪
♪Wait for you with eagerness♪
(Lian Xi, Young Master of Kunlun Mountain)
Your Highness.
♪My love is like ink♪
♪Outlining your silhouette in memories♪
♪Time is ethereal♪
Thank you for your help, Your Lordship.
It's my honor to help you.
I had an appointment with a friend
to paint here,
and happened to see you standing
in the rain like a lost soul.
What on earth happened?
Well, I won't ask anymore.
(Zhang's Steamed Buns)
Are these all your paintings?
Can I take a look?
What a treacherous person!
How dare you entangle with Yan Shuang?
Jiu, let go of him.
Lian Xi?
Tell me, what are you trying to do?
Your Majesty,
I am painting the scenery
in the Mortal Realm,
happened to see Her Highness standing in
the rain, and just gave her a helpful hand.
A helpful hand?
What did you draw?
I can tell at a glance that
you have ulterior motives.
I met Her Highness at
the birthday banquet on Bainiao Island.
She was elegant and generous.
I was impressed and eager to
make friends with her.
(Letter of Challenge)
I do have affection for her,
but I dare not have
any improper thoughts.
You've been thinking about her
since you met her at Bainiao Island.
How dare you say you have
no improper thoughts?
Stop it.
You come here to cause trouble, do you?
No.
Didn't you say
you have something important to discuss?
There is nothing important.
Yan Shuang, I didn't mean to come late.
I was delayed by some important matters
with Feng Yin.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to the Pear Blossom Cottage.
I'll tell you.
I know.
It doesn't matter what caused the delay.
It's getting late. I'm going back first.
It's still raining. Let me send you back.
I want to paint some wind-moving stones
in the Eagle Clan.
Save it.
I am familiar with Yan Shuang.
I will send her back.
Stay away from these
unfamiliar immortals in the future.
They have no good intentions.
Why should I do as you say?
Do you know what I like, what I dislike,
what I want,
and how many friends do I have?
Lord Lian Xi and I feel like old friends
at first sight. We are good friends now.
It's just that you don't know.
You know nothing about me.
How could you make comments on me?
Yan Shuang, what's wrong with you?
Why do you behave
like a different person?
The relationship between immortals
and demons has never been good.
As the princess of the Eagle Clan
in the Immortal Realm,
I shouldn't always
go to your Demon Realm,
to avoid being talked about by others.
I've heard enough rumors and gossip.
For the sake of your reputation
as the Demon King and the Eagle Clan,
I won't go to find you anymore
from now on.
I didn't think you mind the difference
between immortals and demons.
Fine.
Since you think so, just do as you wish.
From now on, let's go separate ways.
Take care.
Let's go.
Father.
How could you forcefully drive your
internal core to enhance immortal power?
If something goes wrong,
your power will collapse.
If your internal core is injured,
your immortal root will be severed.
It is too dangerous to do this.
I thought I could become a demigod with
the help of the Sky-shrouding Umbrella.
I didn't expect to fail.
It's not easy to become a demigod.
If you want to enhance your
immortal power quickly, I'm afraid
you'll have to find another
internal core in the Immortal Realm.
Is there any other powerful internal core
of the deceased immortal?
There is no deceased,
but there are many alive.
Anyway, the aptitude of those immortals
is not as good as yours.
They can never become a god.
Instead of letting them
live a mediocre life,
it's better for you to use it.
In this way, they won't live in vain.
You ask me to take the internal core
of other immortals?
Father, you are asking me to
cultivate devil power?
It's just a way of cultivation.
Absolutely no.
It violates the rule for Acting Heavenly
Empress to cultivate devil power.
If Yuan Qi and Feng Yin know about this,
how could they forgive me?
How could I deserve the trust of Lan Feng
if I do this?
As long as you hold on to your integrity
and resist the temptation of devils,
you are still the Heavenly Empress
who never changes.
Others only see your growing power.
Who knows this secret?
Once I take this shortcut,
I will know the benefit of doing this,
How could I easily
hold on to my integrity?
Shu.
Father,
did you...
Yes, I did use this method.
Now, my immortal spirit
has fully recovered.
My power has also improved a lot
compared to before.
Although I practice devil power,
as long as I hide it well, no one will know.
You didn't discover this, right?
Father, what did you expect me to do
when you decided to do this?
If I punish you, I will be unfilial.
If I don't punish you, it would be unfair.
Shu, all that I did is for you.
If I didn't recover my immortal spirit
as soon as possible,
how could I help you maintain the throne
by handling internal and external matters?
No matter what, there is always
a proper solution.
Why did you choose to
cultivate devil power?
I knew my destiny and
had no ambitions in this life,
but you are different.
You are my outstanding pride.
You are the last hope of our clan.
But unfortunately, you have such a useless
father who lost all his immortal spirit.
Whenever I thought of these, I felt fearful.
In order not to burden you,
I had tried various methods,
but they didn't work, so I...
Shu, think about it again.
Do you know why Lan Feng's body didn't
decay in the coffin for a thousand years?
That's all because I've been
nourishing it with devil power.
I practiced devil power to
help you revive Lan Feng, too.
Can devil power revive Lan Feng?
Yes.
Devils can sacrifice everything
and of course revive everything.
I would not deceive you.
Shu,
everything I do is for you.
Qing Yi, you're back from your training.
Yes, I am.
But what about Martial Aunt?
She hasn't come back yet.
I think you have long forgotten about her.
I heard all about it
on my way here just now.
You are always lingering here,
trying to please Phoenix Queen.
I feel so sorry for Martial Aunt.
Qing Yi, you have grown up.
Now, you are more sensible.
I can't believe I called you Martial Uncle.
You are beyond help.
I should let her know that Qing Yi is back.
Martial Aunt,
you have been gone for a thousand years.
Martial Uncle has changed his mind.
I only hate myself for not being able to
defeat him and take revenge for you.
Martial Aunt, I've been working hard
every day to enhance my immortal power
as you told me.
Don't worry, I'll guard the gate
at all times
and keep the devils away from
Master and everyone else.
This is my tribute to my
Martial…
What?
You were mourning me a minute ago.
Now you can't recognize me?
You are Martial Aunt Yin.
As I traveled the Mortal Realm,
I had been looking for you.
But I had no luck.
I even asked every girl who loves
Pear Blossom Brew and mung bean cakes
whether they are you.
All right, you've passed the age to cry.
Let me taste the Pear Blossom Brew.
Let me taste it.
(Qing Yi and the Water Divine Beast Yin
have a friendship as fellow disciples.)
(If he says anything he shouldn't in front of
Feng Yin and causes a misunderstanding,)
(the marriage between His Godship and
Feng Yin will encounter problems again.)
(I have to let Feng Yin know that
Yin means nothing to His Godship.)
I don't know how much Qing Yi
has told you,
but His Godship is kind and never has
any thoughts of killing without reason.
The Water Divine Beast was his
fellow disciple and died under his sword.
His Godship was only soft-hearted
and found it difficult to accept this reality.
So he always showed concern about this.
In that case,
His Godship didn't protect
the Water Divine Beast as rumored.
There are always
all sorts of rumors outside.
Who else in the entire Three Realms
knows His Godship better than me?
After all, Yin had an ambiguous
relationship with devils,
and caused the deaths of the entire sect
of Daze Mountain.
His Godship insists on finding her
because he wants to find out
the truth of that year.
His waiting for a thousand years is
only for the case?
Of course.
After all, His Godship is a
determined True God.
His Godship never kept Yin in mind
no matter how tricky she was.
It was His Godship himself
who cut her affection back then.
I'm sure His Godship has no love for her,
only hatred.
You ask me to leave. Why?
Qing Yi has finally returned.
We disciples of Daze Mountain
have just gathered together.
I am also a member of Daze Mountain.
Please let me stay.
I don't have the patience to play
another whim trick with Your Godship.
What is a whim trick?
Let me tell Your Godship again.
I am Feng Yin, not Yin.
Stop using Yin's past to entangle me.
Let's get to know each other again
with the identity
of Yuan Qi and Feng Yin, okay?
Feng Yun, see the guest off.
Your Godship.
Your Godship, farewell.
Elder.
Your Godship.
What on earth has happened?
Why is the Phoenix Clan so impolite?
Aunt, why are you here?
I came to see Feng Yin
for the sake of your marriage.
What... what did you say to her?
There are always rumors about you
in the Three Realms.
In case she misunderstands
your past with Yin,
I've come to clarify.
I told her you have nothing but pity
for that Water Divine Beast.
Aunt, what did I tell you before?
Don't get involved in my love affairs.
Why don't you listen?
Your Godship.
I just want to do something good
for Your Godship.
I think you are too
idle in the Qingchi Palace.
Recently, demonic mandrills
are rampant in the East Sea.
I think you'd better go to the East Sea
to quell the chaos caused by them.
With these important matters,
you won't have so much idle time.
I…
Your…
This…
I…
What?
Be a spy?
What a shame for a prestigious weapon!
What's wrong? What happened?
After His Godship knew that
Feng Yin is Yin,
he was just overwhelmed by it.
To win her favor,
he asks me to pry into information
from Fuchen Sword.
We are both weapons.
Why should I do such a cheap thing?
Your Godship,
this method is
good.
Now, there are some clues on
how to save Your Godship.
Shouldn't we try to combine
two good things together?
I've heard Yin talking about it before
in the Hall of Arms.
If she couldn't do something,
she would turn to Fuchen Sword.
I was so envious at that time.
Having such a weapon
can save the master a lot of trouble.
Well, I don't like to force others.
After all, many things rely on talent.
Well, who said I can't do it?
You guys are looking down up on me.
I'll do it.
I will show you that
I am not only good at fighting,
I'm also the best when doing other things.
Your Godship,
it is already the seventh day.
Go into seclusion now.
You are my outstanding pride.
You are the last hope of our clan.
But unfortunately, you have such a useless
father who lost all his immortal spirit.
Whenever I thought of these, I felt fearful.
Devils can sacrifice everything
and of course revive everything.
(Lan Feng, I don't mean to
bend the rules for my father,)
(but no one in this world
loves me as much as you and him.)
In the past thousand years,
you have made a lot of sacrifices for me,
but I couldn't share your worries.
I hope you can stop in time and
don't make the same mistake again.
The race for the heavenly throne
is imminent and all forces are watching it.
Please take good care of yourself, Father.
Be cautious when dealing with others.
Make sure no one notices any clues.
I knew my daughter would protect me.
Don't worry, when I become
the ruler of the Immortal Realm,
I'll let you sit on the
Heavenly Empress's throne.
Report.
Your Lordship, Daze Mountain's disciple
Qing Yi returned to Qingchi Palace
and took a position in the Heavenly Palace
instead of returning to the Mortal Realm.
He stayed in the Heavenly Palace?
Yes.
Do you know what they are planning?
Qing Yi serves in the Hall of Arms.
Those immortal weapons
are very troublesome.
I had no opportunity to enter
and gather information.
Forget it.
Qing Yi is not to be feared.
Keep a close eye on Qingchi Palace.
Report any abnormalities to me.
The Pear Blossom Brew today
doesn't taste well at all.
Will she never come to see me again?
Forget it. She was the one
who got angry first.
I'm not looking for her.
You are here.
You look pretty today.
Jiu, do you want to go to
the Heavenly River with me?
It's not that I want to contact you.
Feng Yin asked me to tell you something.
So I have to talk to you.
Remember to reply to me. I'm waiting for
you at the Pear Blossom Cottage.
When all the immortals gather
at Yuan Qi's birthday banquet,
Feng Yin intends to reinvestigate the case
that happened a thousand years ago.
She needs you to tell the truth
you witnessed back then.
If I successfully clear my name,
it will be a great merit for you.
You can choose any treasure
from our Demon Realm.
Read?
No.
Can't she see the words
"I'm at the Pear Blossom Cottage"?
Alright, Yan Shuang. Let's wait and see.
We are done!
(Clouds Form over Mountains)
Your Highness, the birthday banquet
has been prepared properly.
All immortals and chiefs
have arrived one after another.
Has God Yuan Qi arrived?
No, he hasn't.
Your Highness, does it matter if
His Godship doesn't attend today?
There is no reason for me to withdraw
the invitations I sent out.
If Yuan Qi doesn't come,
find an excuse to cover it up.
What's important is to maintain a
superficial relation with Qingchi Palace.
Even if Yuan Qi doesn't show up,
I've prepared such a big banquet for him,
the immortals will not
discover the truth inside.
Feng Yin wants to reinvestigate
the case that year.
I finally learned from Fu Chen that
they plan to find an opportunity
in the Heavenly Palace.
Opportunity?
You inform Qing Yi to go to the Heavenly
Palace to attend my birthday banquet.
But Master, aren't you uninterested
in the banquet?
I've changed my mind.
Will you reveal the truth a thousand years
ago at the birthday banquet?
The Immortal Realm has concluded
that the destruction of Daze Mountain
and the death of Lan Feng
were caused by collusion between
the demons and the devils.
Although Yuan Qi has found some clues,
and seriously declared Yin's
innocence back then,
the immortals didn't comment on it.
However, they believed in their heart
that His Godship was biased.
Yuan Qi, as a God,
was even treated like this.
You will meet many more difficulties
than you think.
Have you made up your mind?
Yes. I've decided.
I know more details about the past.
It's time to go through the issues among
the immortals, demons and devils
carefully and thoroughly.
You're right.
Aunt.
Have a seat.
Why are you here?
I heard that you want to reinvestigate
the case at the birthday banquet.
I'm here to lend you a helping hand.
I don't need help from others.
But didn't you specifically
ask Hong Yi for help?
Why can't I?
How do you know that
I asked Hong Yi for help?
Since Yuan Qi is here,
let him finish speaking before refusing.
This is Cloud Pearl of Original Chaos.
I made it by refining the fragments of
the Truth Mirror with Chaos Power.
It can lead to the past and
uncover the truth.
Since you have this Cloud Pearl,
why didn't you bring it out earlier?
This is a demigod tool
that I just finished refining.
The tool spirit is still unstable
at the moment.
It may hurt the user if not used properly.
That's why I dare not use it easily.
I'm afraid you will get hurt.
Since you have decided to reinvestigate
the case at the birthday banquet,
it'll be the best time to use it.
Feng Yin,
you can tell me whatever you want to do.
I will definitely stand by your side.
Thank you, Your Godship.
Then, please lend me the Cloud Pearl
at that time.
However, other matters
will remain unchanged.
Farewell.
My disciple is clear about the distinction
between public and private matters.
Sometimes, I don't know whether I should
praise her or not.
You are also an inflexible child.
You two are equally stubborn.
Really?
Why are you still grinning here?
Go chase after her!
Farewell.
This is beautiful.
Yes.
The fragrance smells good.
- It looks so good!
- Look at that.
- Smell this.
- This.
This white flower
smells so good. It's beautiful.
The flowers are so beautiful this year.
That's great.
Your Majesty, Phoenix Queen of Wutong
Island arrives at the Heavenly Palace.
Shall we go and greet her?
I know.
Let the fairy attendants
take good care of her.
I am busy with the preparations
for the birthday banquet.
I have many guests here.
I can't get away.
Ask her to forgive me
if she thinks I neglect her.
Yes.
Your Majesty, the golden peonies
in your Xiuyang Hall
are truly a stunning beauty.
In the Heavenly Palace,
even the whole Immortal Realm, it's
impossible to see such beautiful flowers.
I think these peonies in the garden
are stunning,
but no one can compare to
the beauty of Her Majesty.
That's right.
The person to the heavenly throne will be
selected and appointed soon.
Her Majesty Feng Yuan will hand over
the Seal of the Supreme to Hua Shu.
No matter how beautiful
the blooming flowers are,
they cannot compare to the beauty
of the Heavenly Empress.
This has not been finalized yet. Please
refrain from making such remarks.
Several immortals and the chiefs of
the Three Mountains and Six Palaces
have gone to the South Heaven Gate
to welcome her.
These respected immortals have not
shown up for many years.
They appear as soon as
the Phoenix Queen comes.
Let's go quickly.
Shall we go or not?
I don't know.
I am a junior.
I am ashamed to have you seniors here
to welcome me.
Your Majesty, you can settle disputes
between the two realms at a young age.
We appreciate it so much.
Moreover, Your Majesty inherits
the throne of the Phoenix Queen.
We should come to congratulate you.
Your Majesty didn't want to bother others,
and omitted all the
troublesome formalities.
We shouldn't save the congratulations
when meeting you today.
Thank you for your appreciation.
Please.
Feng Yin.
I looked around just now.
Many immortals are coming here
to welcome you.
They chattered like hundreds of ducks.
It's so noisy.
Will you get out of here now?
They want to meet me so much?
Let's go and meet them then.
Who is this?
Do you know?
No.
Who is this?
It seems she is more powerful than
Her Majesty Hua Shu.
Yu from Qingchi Palace.
Feng Huan from Wutong Island.
Greetings to Your Majesty Hua Shu
and all the immortals.
- It's the Phoenix Queen.
She is the Phoenix Queen.
It's the Phoenix Queen.
- Phoenix Queen.
Greetings to Your Majesty.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪